Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

 Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the http://aquatis.host and Aquatis and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Aquatis include http://aquatis.host, Aquatis, Aquatis, aquatis.host and aquatis.host. The website is a Minecraft Hosting site. By using the Aquatis website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### **TRUSTe Privacy Program**

Aquatis is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence on the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://aquatis.host/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint. TRUSTe may serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

#### **Collection of your Personal Information**

Aquatis will collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, email, address and other personal information. If you purchase Aquatis’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction as well as to fight fraud on our end. Staff members are the only one who view your data. We keep the data on our system for up to 1 year. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Aquatis. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Aquatis website.

Aquatis encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Aquatis so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Aquatis is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Aquatis website.

#### **Use of your Personal Information**

Aquatis collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Aquatis may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Aquatis and its affiliates. Aquatis may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Aquatis does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Aquatis may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Aquatis, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Aquatis will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Aquatis or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Aquatis; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Aquatis, or the public.

#### **Use of Cookies**

The Aquatis website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Aquatis pages, or register with Aquatis site or services, a cookie helps Aquatis to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Aquatis website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Aquatis features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Aquatis services or websites you visit.

#### **Security of your Personal Information**

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Aquatis uses the following:

Comodo

CloudFlare

Paypal

WHMCS

Stripe

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

#### **Children Under Thirteen**

Aquatis does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. We will call the current number to verify.

#### **Changes to this Statement**

Aquatis will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Aquatis encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Aquatis is protecting your information.

#### **Contact Information**

Aquatis welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Aquatis has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Aquatis at:

Aquatis LLC  
Orlando, Florida 34743  
Email Address: [\[email protected\]](https://aquatis.host/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Last Update: 11/05/2020

Copyright © 2016-2024 Aquatis LLC. All Rights Reserved.
